what up stubborn ones welcome back to
the vlog
welcome back to the channel today we're
gonna do something a little different
we're gonna do a little unboxing slash
product review
but before we begin make sure you go
down below and hit that subscribe button
i am on the race to 1
000 subscribers we already passed 500
and that is a great feeling thank you
guys so much for your support
i love you guys so much so
with that being said let's get to it
today we're going to be doing the
unboxing product review of the sun joe
electric pressure washer
this is the spx 2598
and i got this at walmart
so let's see uh
it came equipped
for small jobs so it came with
the surface cleaner which is for your
driveway
or sidewalk or patio deck
whatever you're into let's see here
it's got a nice little handle i like
that
it's got three nozzles it's got a zero
which is this one it's got a
40 degree which is this one
and a 15 degree which is that one
if you're new to pressure washing the
angle is pretty much
how wide or narrow it'll be zero being
the most narrow for further jobs or more
concentrated
uh heavier grease i guess or whatever
you're cleaning i don't know whatever
and 40 being the wider spread so it
makes it better for
cars so you don't mess your paint up
pretty much
let's see here and this is the little
apparatus itself
what's this some kind of handle
a more handle
and the power cord
and then you see is the
sun itself it's actually
very lightweight i like it already
this is gonna be nice for smaller jobs
i'm definitely going to use it
to wash my truck because that thing
it's a it's a big truck so it's really
annoying it takes me a long time i can't
wait
to use it because it comes with its own
phone cannon also
so let's get this thing put together
here we have everything nice and laid
out
and let's get to assembling
right guys so assembly should be easy
because it only comes with a few screws
and there's not that many parts so it
comes with instructions
for you literate people that know
how to read let's get started
first you start with the handle assembly
this part slides right on
and as you see there is a screw here
and there is two screws in the back this
is also part of the assembly
let's go ahead and screw that in it
comes with
whatever however many screws for your
mathematicians
so there's a screw right here in the
middle
hopefully your hands aren't as shaky as
mine
there is one two three
and four screws for this part here
and there's two more right
here
as you see the phone cannon already has
its own little
storage it already comes in there not
bad
and here is
how you control how much soap and water
you're getting
out of the foam cannon not bad
not bad so here is where the
nozzles go
all right so moving on we have the
this is where the the trigger goes it
just slides right in
there's only one way that it can go in
and it slides right into here
it slides right into it it's like
access the knife it slides right into
here
easy peasy and i guess this is the
where the tip goes giggity
slides right there on this side
is where you roll up the power cord
and again it slides one way
boom and as you see
here's where the hose go
slides right in there and you twist
boom easy peasy slimming squeezies
all right guys so this is the trigger
and this slides right in there
as you can see there's only one way to
go in
goes in in and twist
just like that just like that right
there so this is where your high
pressure hose goes
which connects to this side and your
water hose connects to this side
like it says right here it shows a
little picture right there
and it also came with the warning do not
turn it on
without having the water hose connected
it will mess up the engine look at this
look at this thing this thing's so
awesome you just
[Music]
okay guys so everything's hooked up
high pressure water hose
water hose high pressure
all right guys moving on to the phone
cannon i probably have the wrong ratio
read the instructions in your
soap but i'm not that good at math
anyway
maximum salt
let's try out the other tips
so you hold this down tip
in boom just like that
so this is the zero
let's see what it looks like i'm not
gonna do it on the car obviously
okay so make sure that this is in all
the way and this will pop back up
let's try this again
so the zero is for
more precision or further distances
totally cool it's kind of hot out here
should have done this earlier
florida let's do the zero one more time
so that is the zero
15.
the 15 is a little wider than the
zero
that was so satisfying to see and i'm
sweating my
balls off that was so satisfying to see
and i'm sweating my butt off
but it's cool all right guys
final thoughts on the sun joe it's
actually a
pretty nice little machine don't compare
it to the big gas powered
pressure washers obviously but for what
it is the electric motor it
the electric pressure washer it's
actually really good
and walmart had it for their black
friday specials
and i've seen it before on their
rollback specials so that's
it's perfect for that price and as you
saw everything that i did
was not even with the right chemicals so
i'm gonna go out and get
the sidewalk cleaning products and the
actual soap that foams up
and i'm gonna redo another video with
that
but as it is it's perfect for small
jobs and i like it i'll recommend it
i'll give it a nice
a nice rating and i actually already
told my dad about it and he
got himself one too i don't know if he's
used it but
i've used mine and it's cool i like it
and
so thank you guys so much for watching
thank you guys for making to the end of
the video
we are on a race to a thousand
subscribers
and i forgot how to wrap up a video so
this is terrible
but don't forget to like comment
subscribe
and i will see you guys on the next one
peace out
you